play and ultimately channel this time of
i'm going to show you how to use the
using a debugger of bro
as a rebel
so we don't know leading to debugging
and
hospitable insults and it's going to
talk a little lurks
so we go to the
as you know you can try to control
they might use the and then there's some
kind of control called
trees and executing we see that uh...
for it was pretty your
say maybe you could
as the value
which is an anti screen ente script
basically is the right and doesn't
listen couples
abt what to do is you can't debugging
it's mother's day
lunch debugger but because there you can
it put to better news a reflects on all
of us who normally people just right
wingers do you want
and then when i run it
it opens to the bar and disney that
prompted executed the them
and ben
not weaken typing an equal comand here
or use thereof between so the people
here
so for example i can't i can't print
forty-two and print out that the number
forty two
i concede orx too close to forty two
and then as signs that the value
forty-two list either for variable
i condemn
accused of print function again between
adult or i can use to be looking to
held in the bible
pictures of people instantly of the the
same values
certainly assess and evaluate religious
killer
i could also created raise so for
example
here are the names
bwz
and i can uh... printout of the names
is recovering from a
obviously at this is not really good it
doesn't look good
it was
quotation marks around it
and if it's a big matter because not
only today or spaces of
close to print out this way it's
probably all nuclear matter you are
veteran of this x names contains c
values or when value is stays in it
so a better way to to see what's inside
the every
is to use the extreme
often
debugger
and if you could uh... at a reference to
discourage so the state you can print
out this is a reference and they could
preprint other indexes
the uh... the values hussein where you
can they create a hatch
so use to use you have a m
after name
which is the food
and uh...
spending
churches barnett's lee
just for consistency and and dot we have
a hash and david kim
different about the content of these
haitians
is the same too will the x_
at a fugitive
pink out that's ahead for friends and
the keys and uh... the relative for the
respective
italians
it also person so for example
you can do
played is uh... find out how
the bush function restorative potion
and engineering is same moves
you go back
and print out the content of their rate
and you can see that actually
uh... this
got longer and others or pseudonyms for
arguing there
so you can explorer program coordinating
the debugger
and uh... sometimes using the pro-ltte
problems themselves sometimes using the
tools over the order
like printer
and x
it also is there one comes from here so
you can see see you see that you did for
example
if you knew of use eternal peace module
uh... these old functions and then you
can call the nz
cdw dysfunctional thing
and there for me to be calling you
shortlisting because execution returns
the value
so if you want to see the result of this
and mrs
print of the result which is just uh...
current working directory
you could also used another module
for example used raising
filed his name
and uh... it has a busy may have
functioned
diverse consider the return value of
steve
w_j_e_t_
and those things out
and i have to
learned how to spell and that it just
brings out the the the basin a move that
uh... prosecutor
the last part of uh... from france
what if you want to see how this works
so you can put a brake for him
game
on this function
so you want to put up three points on
the file
there is something
basename
is function
and then if i run again this is the big
letter of the
than if i run again distillate
then x's stopped at that point in
we ensure that function
is the basement function into the
business functions of the file these
name class
inches implementing this file that grown
under two hundred fifty eight
you can look at look around
isbell and see the latter rest of the
cold or even the look around from with
zero and two hundred to two hundred
isn't he
and you see uh... some
reliance uniformly
and
not called for so there are not printed
and then the business function
and uh... which works
so you can use a basically
any to you would like uh...
we didn't delivering to explore
profusely
at the end using q
invested in people
i don't like uh...
tutorial villain
and the society's tells solicits
so